Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Graduate School of Arts and Sciences Teaching Fellows Program files, 1975-2015; Accession 2016-A-072
  - John Goldin 10/16/1997 Statistics on Teaching (5 of 5), 1997 October 16 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Teaching Statistics 1997-98, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Dept Statistics 1997-98, 1997-1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - TF Statistics 0809, 2008-2009 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - TF Statistics 0708, 2007-2008 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - TF Statistics 0607, 2006-2007 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - TF Statistics 0506, 2005-2006 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - TF Statistics 0405, 2004-2005 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - TF Statistics 0304, 2003-2004 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - TFP Statistics 2002-03, 2002-2003 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - TFPO Stats 2000-01/2001-02 (1 of 3), 2000-2002 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - TFPO Stats 2000-01/2001-02 (2 of 3), 2000-2002 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - TFPO Stats 2000-01/2001-02 (3 of 3), 2000-2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - TF Statistcs 0203, 2002-2003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - TFP Analyses 0102, 2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - TF Statistics Pre-0102, Pre-2001-2002 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - TFPO Statistics 1999-2000 and Previous Years (1 of 2), Pre-1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - TFPO Statistics 1999-2000 and Previous Years (2 of 2), Pre-1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - TF Statistics, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Summary of TF and PTAI Statistics, 1999 November 9 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - TF Statistics, 1998-1999 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Teaching in Sciences, 1999-2000 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - TF Statistics, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Count by Course, 1995-1996 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - TF Count by Dept, 1994-1995 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Personnel Profile, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - TF by TF Level, 1996-1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Count by Year/Study, 1996-1998 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - English 3 year study, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Registration by Year of Study, 1994-1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Frequency Count, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - TF Stats, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - TF Appts A-E (1 of 3), 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - TF Appts A-E (2 of 3), 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - TF Appts A-E (3 of 3), 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - TF Appts N-Y (1 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - TF Appts N-Y (2 of 2), 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Teaching Fellows PTAI by Dept. Spring 1990 (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Teaching Fellows PTAI by Dept. Spring 1990 (1 of 2) (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Finances, 1999 January-April (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Finances, 1998 September-December (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School Analysis, 1997 August 27 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Graduate School Documents, 1986-1997 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - TF Finances, 2002-2004 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - TF Finances, Pre-1999-2002 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - TF Finances, 2004-2006 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Teaching Appts A-Astro, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Teaching Appts Bio-Chem, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Teaching Appts Classics-Econ, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Teaching Appts Engineering-English, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Teaching Appts EPH-German, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Teaching Appts Hist-Pre Doc., 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Teaching Appts MB, 1993-1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Teaching Appts Psyc-Soc, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Teaching Appts Span-W, 1993-1994 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Teaching Appts A-Classics, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Teaching Appts Comp. Lit-English, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Teaching Appts Epid.-Hist., 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Teaching Appts Hist.-Music, 1994-1995 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - TF Appts Am St-Slavic, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - TF Appts Spanish-Phys, 1996-1997 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Teaching Appointments Phys-Rel Stud, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Teaching Appointments Rel Stud-Women's Studies, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Teaching Appointments History of Art-Math, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Teaching Appointments Math-Philosophy, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Teaching Appointments English-EPH, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Teaching Appointments French-History, 1995-1996 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Teaching Appointments African Studies-Astronomy, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Teaching Appointments Bio-CPSC, 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Teaching Assignments EALL-Engin., 1995-1996 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Teaching Appointments NELC-Psyc, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Teaching Appointments Psyc-Women's Studies, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - TFPO Course Enrollments Teaching Assistants A-I (1 of 3), 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - TFPO Course Enrollments Teaching Assistants A-I (2 of 3), 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - TFPO Course Enrollments Teaching Assistants A-I (3 of 3), 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - TFPO Course Enrollments Teaching Assistants J-W (1 of 3), 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - TFPO Course Enrollments Teaching Assistants J-W (2 of 3), 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - TFPO Course Enrollments Teaching Assistants J-W (3 of 3), 2002-2003 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Teaching Fellow Survey Spring 1999 (1 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Teaching Fellow Survey Spring 1999 (2 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Teaching Fellow Survey Spring 1999 (3 of 3) (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Enrollments, 1998-2003 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Enrollments, 1998-2003 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Enrollments, 1998-2003 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Enrollments Notes, 1999 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - TFS Planning Fall 2010 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - TFS Planning Spring 2010 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - TFS Planning Spring 2011 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - TFS Planning Fall 2011 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - TFS1 Fall 2009-Spring 2015, 2009-2015 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - TFMS TF Types by Department Meetings Scheduled, 2009-2015 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - TFMS TF Types Codes and Data Sample Chart, 2009-2015 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - TFMS Users: Read Write Access, 2009-2015 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - TFS Planning Reports, 2009-2015 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Yale Project Charter FY12, 2011-2012 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - TFS Feedback Fall 2009 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - TFS Training Allocations Launch, 2012 April (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Fall 2010 Revisions to Appt Ltrs (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Departmental Allocations Appointment Letters, 2009-2015 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Memo Teaching Fellow Liaisons, 2009-2015 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Yale College RCSP, 2010-2011 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - TFP Overview, 2014 May (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - TFWAG Spring 2013 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - TFMS Meetings, 2009-2015 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - TFS Training Phase I II, 2009 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - TFS Problems to Follow Up Spring 2010 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Revising TF Assignments, 2009-2015 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - TFS Instructions Phase 1 Allocations and Phase 2 Assignments, 2009-2015 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - TFS Instructions Phase 3 GSPS PMT, 2009-2015 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Teaching Fellow Program Management System, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Teaching Fellow System, 2008 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Teaching Fellow's Handbook, 1989-2001 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Teaching Fellow's Handbook, 1991-1998 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Becoming Teachers, 1999-2005 (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - TF Handbook, 1998-1999 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - TF Handbook, 1999-2000 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - TF Handbook, 2000-2001 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - TF Handbook, 2001-2002 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - TF Language X Curriculum, 2004-2007 (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - TF P P, 2003-2005 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - TF Website, 2002-2005 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - TFWAG, 2002-2005 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - TFWAG, 2005-2008 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - TFWAG, 1999-2002 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - TF Project Committee, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - TFWAG, 2004-2006 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - TFWAG, 2000-2006 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - TF Undergreaduate AIS, 1999-2001 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - ALS, 2009-2010 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - TFs on Transcripts, 2002 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - TF Undergraduate Course Graders, 2005-2008 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - TF Writing Intensive, 2005-2006 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - TF Process, 1999-2002 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - TF Process, 2003-2006 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - TFS Section Registrations, 2003-2009 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Section Registrations, 2007-2008 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Section Registrations, 2006-2007 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - TF Process Papers, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Individualized Letters, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Allocations, 1998-1999 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - 1998-1999 Fall/Spring Clean Up (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - TF Evaluations, 2003-2005 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - TF Evaluations, 2005-2008 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - TF Finances, 2006-2008 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Graduate School, 2007 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - NRC Survey, 2006 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Chronological File, 1999-2000 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Committee on the Evaluation of Graduate Teaching, 2002-2003 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - BBS, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Enrollment Proj., 1993-1994 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - TFP 2.3/2, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - 3.5 Upgrade Spring, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - 3.5 Upgrade Fall, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - TF 3.5s, 1997-1998 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - TF2 Survey, 1993 June (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - 3.5 Study, 1998-1999 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - 3.5 Study, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - 3.5 Study, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - TF Appointments Fall 1998 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - 3.5 Teaching Appointments Fall 1998 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 3.5 Committee Report, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - TF Program Review Committee, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Departmental TF Committees, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Divinity T. Fellows, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - TFP Eligibility, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - PTAI Requests Allocations, 2005-2006 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Part-Time Acting Instructor Trends, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - PTAI Issues, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Professional Students, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Teacher Preparation and Development, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Trends - Retention, 1997-2000 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Data Gathering Group, 1996-1997 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Other Schools Research, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Enrollments by Year of Study, 1994-1996 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Time to Degree, 1992-1993 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Committee To Surveys TFs, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Committee on Teaching by Graduate Standards, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Diss. Fsp. Completion, 1992-1994 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Diss. Fsp. Completion, 1991-1992 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Diss. Fsps. Completion, 1990-1991 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Completion Study, 1988-1992 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Various Dissertation Fellowships, 1990-1992 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Mellon Statistics, 1991-1996 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - TF/Diss. Fsps, 1989-1994 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - UDF Proj. 5 Years, 1992-1998 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - University Council Memo, 2000 September 15 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - 6th Year Study Revision, 1997 August 27 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - 6yr Study, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Materials Sent to Tom Rick 95 Ani, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - WEB Verification Survey, 2008-2009 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Verifications, TCHG Spring 2005 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Verifications Teaching Fall 2005 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Verifications TCHG, Spring 2004 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Verifications, TCHG, Fall 2003 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Verifications, TCHG, Spring 2003 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Verifications, TCH, Fall 2002 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Verifications, TCHG, Spring 2002 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Verifications, TCHG, Fall 2001 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Verifications, TCHG, Spring 2001 (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Verifications, TCHG, Fall 2000 (1 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Verifications, TCHG, Fall 2000 (2 of 2) (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - TF Verification, 2003-2004 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - TF Verification, 2005-2006 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - TF Verification, 2007-2008 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - TF Verification, 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Verification Survey Spring 2012 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Verification Survey, 2011 March (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Verification Survey, 2011 January (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Verification Survey, 2010 March (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Verification Survey, 2008 March (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - PTF Teaching, 2005-2013 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Prize Teaching FSP, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - PTF Nomination Letters for Fellows Selected, 2002-2003 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Prize Teaching FSP Special Notes, 2003 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Prize Teaching Fellowships, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Prize Teaching FSP Dinner, 2003 November 20 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Prize Teaching FSP Dinner, 2002 November 21 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Prize Teaching FSP Dinner, 2001 November 15 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Prize Teaching Fellowship Dinner, 2000 December 11 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - PTF Nomination Letters for Fellows Selected, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Prize Teaching Fellowship Selected Nomination Letters, 2001-2002 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Prize Teaching FSP Selected, 2000-2001 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Prize Teaching Fellows, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Prize Teaching Fellowship Nomination Letters, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Prize Teaching Fellowship All Nomination Letters from Students, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Prize Teaching Fellowship, 1999-2000 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Prize Teaching, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Prize Teaching Fellows Dinner, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Prize Teaching Fellow Dinner, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Prize Teaching Fellows Selected in 2009-2010 for 2010-2011, 2009-2011 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Prize Teaching Fellowship Recipients, 2009-2010 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Prize Teaching Fellowship Recipients, 2009-2010 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Prize Teaching Fellows Award Conferred, 2008-2009 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - PTF Nominaaions Not Eligible Teaching Awarded, 2008-2010 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Prize Teaching Fellows, 2008-2009 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Teaching Fellow Prize, 2008 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Prize Teaching Fellows, 2007-2008 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Prize Teaching Fellows Nominated, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Prize Teaching Fellowship Spring 2005 Nominees for 2005-06, 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - PTF Award Ltrs, 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - PTF Not Eligible, 2005-2006 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - PTF List of Nominees from Previous Years, 1999-2006 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - PTF Dinner, 2006 November 1 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Prize Teaching Fellows for 2004-2005 AY Award Dinner, 2005 November 30 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Prize Teaching Fellowship Dinner, 2004 November 1 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Prize Teaching Nominations Spring 2005-Not Awarded (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Prize Teaching Fellows Award Recipients, 2004-2005 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - PFT Award Letters, 2004-2005 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Prize Teaching Dinner, 2009 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - PTF Dinner, 2008 November 5 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Prize Teaching Fellowship Dinner, 2007 November 28 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Prize Teaching FSP Selected, 2003-2004 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - PTF Nomination Letters, 2004-2005 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Questionnaire Letter to Students, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Granparenting, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Garner Plan, 1978-1988 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Educ. Final Rpts, 1991-1998 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Head TF, 1994 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Kagan/Pollitt Plan, 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Mentoring of Graduate Students. Faculty of Arts and Sciences., 1999 February (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Move, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Review of Graduate Education, 1997 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Prown CTe Report, 1990-1992 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Prown Report General Plan Prown Committee, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Prown Report Kagan-Pollit -- Memoranda, 1978 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Teaching Fellow Office, 1996 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Title IX, 1980-1981 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - University Tribunal, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Dean's Memo Fall 2010 Spring 2011, 2010-2011 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - TFP Allocations Appointments Process, 2010-2011 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Dean's Memo-Fall 2009 and Spring 2010, 2009-2010 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Dean's Memo Fall Spring 2007-08, 2007-2008 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - TFP Appointment Process Memos Fall Spring 08-09, 2008-2009 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Fall 2007 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Dean's Memo Spring 2006 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Dean's Memo Fall 2006 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Fall 2005 Appointments (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Appointments Memo Spring 2005 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Teaching Appointments Spring 2005; Updated through March 14, 2005 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Fall Appointments Memos, 2004 June 21 (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Dean's Memo Fall 2004 (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Deans' Memos, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Sections Survey Memos, 2002-2003 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Spring Appointments Memos, 2003 December 2 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Fall Appointments Memos, 2003 June 18 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Deans' Memo, 2001-2002 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Fall Appointments Memo Mailing, 2000 July 24 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Spring Appointments Memo Mailing, 2000 November 15 (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Deans' Memos Spring 04, 2004 (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Deans' Memos Fall 03, 2003 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Dean's Memo, 2001 January 5 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Deans' Memo to Faculty (Brodhead and Hockfield), 2000 September 5 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Dean's Memo Spring 2001 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Dean's Fall Memo, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - TF Appointments, 1999-2004 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - TF Dean's Memo, 1999-2008 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Dean's Spring Memo, 2000 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Deans' Memo, 1999 September 9 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - TF Fall Dean's Review, 1999 September 23 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Appointments Spring 1999 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Provost (Letter only), 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Fall Process Memo, 1992-1994 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Fall Process Memo, 1998 March 5 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Fall Process Memo, 1994 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Dean's Memoranda, 1993-1998 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - FAS JLS Project, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Allocations Memos, 1993-2010 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Teaching Fellow Program Mailings, 2003-2004 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - TFP Mailings, 1997-2003 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - WR, 2011-2012 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - WR Courses, 2010-2011 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - WR Courses, 2009-2010 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - WR, 2008-2009 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Writing Requirement Courses, 2007-2008 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Bass Writing, 2006-2007 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Bass Writing Program, 2005-2006 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - WR, 2005-2006 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Bass Writing Program, 2004-2005 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Writing Intensive, 1999-2004 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - TFP Res. Col., 2002-2003 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - On-Line Course Evaluations, 2010 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - On-Line Discussion Section Selection System, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - TF Enrollments Fall 2009 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Discussion Sections Fall 09, 2009 (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Discussion Sections Spring 2008 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - On-Line Section Registration Fall, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Discussion Sect. Fall, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - OCE, 2009 January (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - TF Enrollment Questions Spring, 2009 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Online Evaluations, 2008 March (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - OCE Spring, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Error List Spring, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Error List Fall, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - On-Line Course Evaluations Process, Undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - OCE Fall, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - OCE (and CRN Error Rpts) Spring, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Error Rpts Fall, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - OCE, 2006 March (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - OCE, 2006 January (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - OCE, 2005 March (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - OCE Spring, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - OCE Fall, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - OCE, 2004 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Fixing, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Enrollments Verification Spring, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - TFS Course Enrollments Fall, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - TF Enrollments Spring, 2007 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - TF Enrollments Review Fall, 2006 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Teaching Appointments Reports Spring, 2005 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Teaching by Doctoral Students - Expected Actual, 1998-2002 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Teaching Fellow Statistics, 1999-2005 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Non-GSPS Appointments A-G, 2010 January (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Non-GSPS Appointments H-M, 2010 January (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Non-GSPS Appointments N-Z, 2010 January (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Non-GSPS Appointments Processed A-G Spring, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Non-GSPS Appointments Processed N-Z Spring, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Non-GSPS Appointments Processed H-M Spring, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Non-GSPS Appointments P:rocessed A-G, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Non-GSPS Appointments Processed H-M, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Non-GSPS Appointments Processed N-Z, 2008-2009 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - AFAM, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - AMST, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - ANTH, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - CHEM, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - CLSS, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - CPLT, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - CPSC, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - DIV, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - EALL, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - ECON, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - EEB, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - ENAS, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - ENGL, 2009-2010 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - FILM, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - FREN, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - F, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Genetics, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - GMAN, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - GEOL, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - HIST, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - HSAR, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - HSHM, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Humanities, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - INST INRL, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - ITAL, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - MATH, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - MCDB, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - MD/PH.D., 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - MGT, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - MUSI, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - NELC, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - OPRS, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - PLSC, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - PHIL, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - PHYS, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - PSYC, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - RCSP, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - RLST, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - SAST, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - SLAV, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - SOCY, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - SPPR, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - STAT, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - WGSS, 2009-2010 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - American Studies Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - African American Studies Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Anthropology Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Applied Physics Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Astronomy Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - BBS Track Courses, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - Chemistry Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - Classics Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - Comparative Literature Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - Computer Science Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - East Asian Languages Literatures Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Ecology Evolutionary Bilology Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Economics Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Engineering Applied Science Appointments Processed, 2008-2009 (Box 16, Folder 45)